Park Place, The Gallery of Art Research, Inc. and Paula Cooper Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Paula Cooper Gallery, 1962-2006, Series 3:; (Boxes 4-49, 51; 45.7 linear feet)
  - Artists' Files, 1962-2006, bulk mid-1970s-early 2000s, 3.3:
    - Stella, Frank, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Tobias, Julius, Slides, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Torrfield, Marvin, circa 1977 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Van Buren, Richard, circa 1971-1978, (Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 7) (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - White, Joseph, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - White, Joseph (Box 45)
      - Collections, circa 1970s (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Exhibitions, circa 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Biography, circa 1973 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Reviews, circa 1970s (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Wilmarth, Chris, 1968-1973 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Wilmarth, Chris (Box 45)
      - Reviews, circa 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Biography and Bibliography, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Collections, circa 1970s (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1977, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Information About Artwork, circa 1970s (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - Dealer-Artist Agreement, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 28)
      - Photographs, circa 1970s (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Wudl, Tom, circa 1975-1979 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Zaims, Stephen, Photographs, circa 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Zapkus, Keytutis (Kes) (Box 45)
      - Cards, circa 1971-1984, (2 folders) (Box 45, Folder 32-33)
      - Reviews, 1973-1979 (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition List, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - Miscellaneous, 1975, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - Collections, circa 1979 (Box 45, Folder 37)
      - Biography, circa 1971-1980 (Box 45, Folder 38)
      - The Contemporary Art Center, Cincinnati, OH (June 28 - Aug. 20, 1978), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Zapkus, Keytutis (Kes), Correspondence, 1962-1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 46)
      - Miscellaneous Materials, 1969-1971, (Includes Allen Kaprow's "Al's Grand Hotel") (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Artistes (Oct.-Nov. 1979) [Journal], 1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - "L'Annunciazione di Antonelle" Exhibition Catalog, Museo Nazionale di Palazzo Bellomo- Siracusa, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - 1993-1994 Exhibitions Notebook [Unbound], circa 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Diderot, Photos from Galerie Mikro, Berlin, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Slides, Unknown and Unlabeled, circa 1960s-2000s (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Negatives, Paula Cooper Installations [179 and 198], circa 1960s-2000s, (2 boxes housed in a shoebox) (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Campus, Peter, Oversized Contact Sheets, Available Works, 1998, (Oversized material from Box 24, Folder 54) (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Kuehn, George, Oversized Photograph, undated, (Oversized material from Box 26, Folder 22) (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Leavengood, David, Oversized Photographs, circa 1971, (Oversized materials housed in Box 26, Folder 23) (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Shields, Alan, Oversized Color Photographs, circa 1972-1990s, (Oversized materials from Box 38, Folder 28) (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Van Buren, Richard, Oversized Drawing, circa 1971, (Oversized material from Box 45, Folder 15) (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records, 1967-1984, 1992-1996, 3.4:
    Found are sales invoices from 1967-1976 and 1981-1984, consignment records from the early to mid-1990s, payment ledgers from 1972-1983, cancelled checks, deposit receipts, general ledgers, tax files, and paid bills. Additional renovation bills and paid bills are found in Business Records. Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - Cancelled Checks (Nov. 1968 - May 1969), 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Cancelled Checks, 96 Prince Street (Apr. - Nov. 1970), 1970, (2 folders) (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
    - Cancelled Checks, 96 Prince Street (Dec. 1970 - Dec. 1971), 1970-1971, (3 folders) (Box 47, Folder 3-5)
    - Consignment Sheets and Purchase Records, 1992-1996, (5 folders) (Box 47, Folder 6-10)
    - Deposit Receipts, 1968-1972 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Fabrication Agreements and Estimates, 1967-1974 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Federal Quarterly Tax Return, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Frame Forwarding, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Framing Invoices, 1971-1984, (2 folders) (Box 47, Folder 15-16)
    - General Ledger (Oct. 1968 - Aug. 1969), 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Hafers [Invoices], 1975 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Ledger, 1968-1970, (Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 8) (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Paid Bills (Jan. - Dec. 1970), 1968-1970, (2 folders) (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Payment Ledgers (Jan. 1972 - June 1979, June 1980 - Nov. 1983), 1972-1983, (6 folders) (Box 48, Folder 3-8)
    - Sales Book, circa 1968-1980 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Sales Invoices [Nos. 1111-2293], 1967-1974, (7 folders) (Box 48, Folder 10-16)
    - Sales Invoices [Nos. 2294-2524], 1974-1976, (2 folders) (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - Sales Invoices [Nos. 2525-2528], Orange, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Sales Invoices, 1981-1984, (3 folders) (Box 49, Folder 4-6)
    - Sales Invoices, Voided, 1970-1982 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Taxes (FYE Aug. 31, 1969), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Oversized Ledger, 1968-1970, (Oversized material from Box 47, Folder 19) (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials, 1966-1980, 1991, 3.5:
    This series contains newspaper and magazine clippings about artists, the gallery, Paula Cooper, and exhibitions; an interview transcript; and, a copy of a manuscript. Most of the printed materials related to specific artists are filed in the Artists' Files subseries. Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - Clippings, 96 Prince Street, 1966-1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Clippings and Interview Transcript re: Paula Cooper, 1969-1980 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Lippard, L. and A. Martin. "Fire in the Lake," Vol. 1, No. 5, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 12)